Sheerlin Vuong

Tel (mob): 07463213859 E-mail: sheerlinvuong@gmail.com

Personal Profile

I am a diligent and open-minded individual with strong work ethics and have shown myself to work effectively and responsibly within a team. I aim to combine experience, initiative, and enthusiasm in my profession and everything I do.

Education

2014 – 2017: Swansea University

Electrical and Electronic Engineering (BEng): First Class Honours (1st)

2012 - 2014: Lambeth Academy Sixth Form

A-levels: Mathematics (B), Chemistry (C), Physics (D)

2007 - 2012: Ashcroft Technology Academy

GCSEs: 9 A* - C including Mathematics (A), Science (B), French (B),

Business studies (B) BTEC: Engineering (Merit Award)

Work Experience

October 2016 - Catering Assistant at Liberty Stadium

- Efficiently serving customers in a fast-paced environment
- Providing great customer service and quickly dealing with problems
- Handling cash and operating tills
- Maintaining the shop floor through cleaning and replenishing stock

October 2015 – April 2017: Student Ambassador at Swansea University

- Representing the university on open/visit days and ensuring a lively and positive experience
- Tour guide for prospective students and parents
- Responsible for answering any questions and providing information

August 2010-May 2012: Volunteer at Cancer Research Charity Shop

- Fundraiser: Planned new and interesting ideas to raise money within a team as well as organizing fundraising events on the high street
- Sales Assistant: Provided well-mannered customer service
- Managing, stocking and cleaning the shop floor
- Handing the cash machine and counting the profit at the end of the day
- Administrative skill when putting customer information into the subscription database

August 2010: Larkhall Children's Centre

- Attended to the needs of children under 5
- Learned about health and safety in the kitchen when preparing lunch for children
- Looking out for hazards when organising and cleaning the play areas

Skills and Qualities

- Python
- Basic HTML, CSS and C
- Microsoft Excel
- Can speak fluent Cantonese
- Intermediate Mandarin I had the opportunity to study Mandarin as well as partaking in cultural activities in China at Weihai University.

Additional Information

- Prefect at Ashcroft Technology Academy Maintaining the disciplinary standards within the academy and developing communication skills by helping younger students to read.
- Achieved Grade 5 piano, as well as tutoring children how to play piano. –
 Demonstrates patience, persistence, and determination when challenged with more difficult pieces.
- W Renwick Prize for the Best Software-based Project by Swansea College of Engineering for my third year project.